Guide to the John William Davis Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- 1918-1921, Series II; 2.5 linear feet (6 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - MacAfee, John Blair, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - MacAlister, Sir Donald, bart., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - MacCorkle, William A., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - McCoy, Paul, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - McCoy, Walter I., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - McDonald, Peerce N., 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - MacDonald, Rose M., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - McKenna, Stephen, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Maclean, Sir Donald, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - McReynolds, James Clark, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Marbury, William L., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Marlborough, Consuelo (Vanderbilt), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Merry del Val, Alphonso, Marquis de, 1918-1919, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Mersey, John Charles Bigham, 1st viscount, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Middle Temple, 1919, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Midleton, Digby Wentworth Bayard Willoughby, 9th baron, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Monod, Francois, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Moore, Charles F., 1919-1921 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Moulton, John Fletcher Moulton, 1st baron, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Mount Edgcumbe, Piers Alexander Hamilton Edgcumbe, 5th earl of, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Murray, Arthur (Cecil), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Murray, Sir John, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Northcliffe of Isle of Thanet, Alfred Charles William Harmsworth, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Ochs, Adolph Simon, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - O'Connor, Thomas Power, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - O'Laughlin, J. C., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Ormathwaite, Arthur Henry John Walsh, 3rd baron, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Osler, Sir William, bart, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Oxford and Asquith, Herbert Henry Asquith, 1st earl of (Box 10, Folder 60)
      See: box 8, folder 6
    - Palmer, Alexander Mitchell, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Parker, Alton Brooks, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Parker, Sir Gilbert, bart, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Peddicord, Charles E., 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Perkins, William Robertson, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Perley, Sir George Halsey, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Pershing, John Joseph, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Peters, Andrew James, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Phillimore of Shiplake, Walter George Frank Phillimore, 1st baron, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Phillips, William, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Pierce, J., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Pilgrims, The, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Polk, Frank Lyon, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Polk, Frank Lyon, 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Powell, Francis E., 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Preston, Lillian (Davis), 1919 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Putnam, George Haven, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Queenborough, Almeric Hugh Paget, 1st baron, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Reading, Rufus Daniel Isaacs, 1st marquis of, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Reay, Donald James Mackay, 11th baron, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Reay, David C., 1919, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Richardson, Hilary Goode, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Riddell of Walton Heath, George (Allardice) Riddell, 1st baron, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Robinson, James W., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Rogers, John Jacob (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Root, Elihu, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Roper, Daniel C., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Rothermere, Harold Sidney Harmsworth, 1st viscount, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Rushmore, Charles E., 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Russell, Charles Howland, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Rutland, Henry John Brinsley Manners, 8th duke of, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Ryle, Herbert Edward, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Sackville, Lionel Edward Sackville West, 3rd baron, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Sackville-West, Victoria Mary, 1919, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Sandhurst, William Mansfield, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Saulsbury, Willard, 1918-1920 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Scott, James Brown, 1918, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Seely, John Edward Bernard, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Shaver, Clement Lawrence, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Shaw of Dunfermline, Thomas Shaw, baron, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Sherley, Swagar, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Shields, Randolph T., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Shipley, Sir Arthur Everett, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Shoecraft, Eugene, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - [Simon, Sir John Allsebrook], [1919] (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Sims, William Snowden, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Skinner, Robert P., 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Society of the Dilettanti, 1919, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Soulsby, Sir William Jameson, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Sterne, Lawrence, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Stone, Melville Elijah, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Storey, Charles M., 1918 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Swartz, Osman E., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Szold, Robert, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Tarkington, Booth [to Ellen (Bassell) Davis], 1919 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Taylor, C. Burgess, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Templeman, E. Bryan, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Thompson, Huston, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Todd, George Carroll, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Tucker, Henry St. George, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Tyrrell, Sir William George, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Underwood, E. Marvin, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Vance, J. Carl, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Wakefield, Sir Charles Cheers, bart., 1918 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Walker, Stuart W., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Wallace, George S., 1918 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Wallace, Hugh Campbell, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Wallace, William, Jr., 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Wardwell, Allen, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Warren, Charles, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Watson, Charles Wayland, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Watson, Katherine L., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - White, Edward D., 1919 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - White, George, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - White, Henry, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Wickersham, George Woodward, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Wile, Frederic William, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Willard, Joseph Edward, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Wright, J. Butler, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Unidentified, 1918-1921 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Oversize, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Special files
    - Diplomatic memoranda and copies of official correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Proceedings of the Inter-Allied Commission on the Rhineland, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Diplomatic memoranda and copies of correspondence of the Inter-Allied Commission on the Rhineland, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 89)
      See: box 10, folder 71; box 8, folder 27; box 9, folder 37; box 10, folder 85
    - Diplomatic memoranda and copies of official State Department Correspondence, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Diplomatic memoranda concerning a treaty dispute between Bolivia and Chile, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Diplomatic memoranda concerning a treaty dispute between Bolivia and Chile, with an opinion by JWD, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Diplomatic memoranda and copies of official State Department correspondence, 1921, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Embassy engagement book for formal luncheons and dinners, 1918-1921 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Engagement book, 1918-1921 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Newspaper clippings about JWD, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Programs and menus for luncheons and dinners attended by JWD, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Programs and menus for luncheons and dinners attended by JWD, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Programs and menus for luncheons and dinners attended by JWD, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Programs for miscellaneous ceremonial occasions, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Diaries
    - 1918 August 23-1919 August 30 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - 1919 August 31-1920 April 6 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - 1919 April 7-August 12 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - 1920 August 13-1921 March 15 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - 1919 (datebook) (Box 13, Folder 105)
- Correspondence, 1921-1923; Series III; 4.5 linear feet (11 boxes)
  Select correspondence is in alphabetical order. General correspondence and financial correspondence are in separate chronological sequences. There may be additional correspondence from this period filed by topic in Series VII, VIII, and XI.
  - Select correspondence
    - Adams, Julia McDonald (Davis) (Mrs. William McM.), 1921, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Adams, William McM., 1923 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Adkins, Jesse C., 1921, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committee of One Hundred on Indian Affairs (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Aikins, Sir James, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      See also: box 14, folder 3
    - Alexander, Charles B. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      See: box 16, folder 40
    - American Bar Association, 1921 April-December (Box 14, Folder 3)
      See: box 15, folder 27; box 15, folder 29; box 15, folder 31; box 16, folder 44; box 19, folder 108
    - American Bar Association, 1922 January - 1923 May 15 (Box 14, Folder 4-14)
    - American Bar Association, 1923 May 16-November (Box 15, Folder 15-19)
    - American Bar Association, 1923 December (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - American Committee for the Independence of Armenia (Box 15, Folder 20)
      See: box 17, folder 68
    - American Law Institute, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - American Peace Award, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      See also: box 15, folder 31
    - American Society of International Law, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Andrews, Matthew Page, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      See: box 17, folders 53-60
    - Angell, Montgomery, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish (Box 15, Folder 23)
      See: box 16, folder 40; box 17, folders 63-65
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, The, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Astor, Nancy Witcher (Langhorne) Astor, viscountess, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Atchison, Topeka and Sante Fe Railway Company, The, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Baker, Sir George Sherston, bart, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Baker, Newton Diehl, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Balfour, Arthur James, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Barratt, Sir John Arthur, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Baruch, Bernard M., 1921-1922 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Bassell, Cornelia B., 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Battle, George Gordon, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      See: box 16, folder 49
    - Beck, James M., 1921, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      See: box 14, folder 3
    - Bedford, Alfred Cotton, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Birkenhead, Frederick Edwin Smith, 1st earl of, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Bliss, Robert Woods (Box 15, Folder 31)
      See: box 17, folders 63-65
    - Bliss, Tasker Howard (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Bok, Edward William, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Breckinridge, Desha, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Breckinridge, Henry, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Brown, Izetta Jewel, 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Brown University, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Buffham, John H., 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Bullen, Percy Sutherland, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Bullitt, William Marshall, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Burnham, Harry Lawson Webster Lawson, 1st viscount, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 16, Folder 34)
      See: box 16, folder 35
    - Byrne, James, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      See: box 16, folder 38
    - Canfield, Cass (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Cecil of Chelwood, Edgar Algernon Robert Cecil, 1st viscount (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Chadbourne, Thomas L., 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1921-1922 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Chile, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - China Society of America, The, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Choate, Mabel, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Clayton, Henry D., 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Colby, Bainbridge, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Coolidge, Archibald Cary (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Coolidge, Louis Arthur, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Cornwell, John J., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Coudert, Frederic Rene, 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 41-42)
    - Cox, James M., 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Crane, Robert Newton, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Cravath, Paul D. (Box 16, Folder 44)
      See: box 16, folder 40; box 17, folders 53-60
    - Crewe, Robert Offley Ashburton Crewe-Milnes, 1st marquis of, 1921-1922 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Curzon of Kedleston, George Nathaniel Curzon, 1st earl of, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Daniels, Josephus, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Dartmouth College, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Davis, Emma Kennedy, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Davis, J. Horner, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Davis, Norman H., 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Davison, Harry Pomeroy, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Delano, Frederic Adrian (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Democratic State Executive Committee, West Virginia, 1921-1923 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Depew, Chauncey Mitchell (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Desborough, William Henry Grenfell, 1st baron, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Desvernine, Raoul E., 1921, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Dodge, Cleveland E., 1922 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1922 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Duggan, Stephen Pierce (Box 16, Folder 51)
      See: box 16, folder 40; box 17, folders 63-65; box 18, folder 72; box 18, folder 95
    - Edwards, Agustin, 1921, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Embree, Edwin Rogers (Box 16, Folder 52)
      See: box 18, folder 97
    - English-Speaking Union, 1921-1923 (Box 17, Folder 53-60)
    - Esterline, Blackburn, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Ewing, Thomas, 1921-1923 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Fahey, John H. (Box 17, Folder 61)
      See: box 16, folder 37
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1921-1923 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Finlay of Nairn, Robert Bannatyne Finlay, 1st viscount, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Finley, John Huston, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Fish, Stuyvesant (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Fletcher, Henry P., 1921 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Flexner, Abraham, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Follansbee, Mitchell D., 1922-1923 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1922 July - 1923 (Box 17, Folder 63-65)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1922-1923 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1923 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Garrison, Lindley M., 1921 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Gary, Hampson, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Gay, Edwin F. (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Geddes, Sir Auckland Campbell, 1921-1923 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Geddes, Sir Eric (Campbell), 1923 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Gerard, James Watson, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Granville, Granville George Leveson Gower, 3rd earl of, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Graves, Charles A., 1923 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Gregory, Thomas Watt, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Grossman, Moses H., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 68)
      See: box 15, folder 27
    - Guthrie, William D., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Halley, Samuel H., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Harrison, Pat (Byron Patton), 1922 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Houston, Hale, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Hudson, Manley Ottmer, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 71)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 16, folder 35
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1921, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 71)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 17, folders 53-60
    - Hughes, William Joseph, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Hull, Cordell (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Huntley, Theodore A., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Institute of International Education, The, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Johnson, George W., 1922 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Johnston, J. W., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine Jules, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Kellogg, Frank Billings, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - King, William Lyon Mackenzie (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Knaebel, Ernest, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Lamar, William H., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Lamont, Thomas William, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Lang, Cosmo Gordon Lang, baron, Abp. of Canterbury, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Lape, Esther Everett, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 77)
      See: box 15, folder 22
    - László de Lombos, Philip Alexius, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Lee of Fareham, Arthur Hamilton, Lee, 1st viscount, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Leffingwell, Russell Cornell, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 78)
      See: box 18, folder 85
    - Lewis, William Draper (Box 18, Folder 78)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 15, folder 21
    - Lloyd George, David, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Long, Breckinridge, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Lowden, Frank Orren, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Lowell, A. Lawrence (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - MacDonald, Angus, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - McDonald, Anne Yates, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - McDonald, Marshall W., 1921 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - McDonald, Peerce N., 1921 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - MacDonald, William, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Mackay, Clarence H., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - McReynolds, James Clark, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Manton, Martin T., 1921 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Mayo, Katherine, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Midleton, Digby Wentworth Bayard Willoughby, 9th baron, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Miles, Basil, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Miller, Nathan L. (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Montague, Gilbert M., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Moore, Charles F., 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Moore, John Bassett, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Moore, Robert Walton, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Murray, Arthur (Cecil), 1922 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - National Bank of Commerce in New York, 1921, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - National Budget Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - National League of Women Voters, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Nesbitt, Wallace, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - New, Harry S., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - New York County Lawyers' Association, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - New York State Bar Association, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Oliphant, Herman (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Page, Thomas Nelson, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Palmer, A. Mitchell (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Parker, Alton Brooks (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Pepper, George Wharton (Box 18, Folder 88)
      See: box 14, folder 3;box 17, folders 53-60
    - Pershing, John Joseph, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Peters, Andrew James, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Phillips, William, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Pilgrims, The, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Post, Melville D., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Preston, John J. D., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Preston, Lillian (Davis), 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Preston, Walter C., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Princeton University, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Putnam, George Haven, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Queenborough, Almeric Hugh Paget, 1st baron, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Randolph, Hollins N., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Reading, Rufus Daniel Isaacs, 1st marquis of, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Redfield, William C., 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Reed, David A., 1922 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Reid, Ogden M., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Reynolds, James Bronson (Box 18, Folder 95)
      See: box 15, folder 21
    - Rhodes Scholarship Trust, The, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Richardson, Hilary Goode, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Robinson, Sir Harry Perry, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Robinson, Joseph Taylor, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Rockefeller, John Davison, Jr., 1922 (Box 18, Folder 96)
      See: box 17, folders 63-65; box 18, folder 97
    - Rockefeller Foundation, The, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, The, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Roper, Daniel C., 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Root, Elihu (Box 19, Folder 99)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 15, folder 22
    - Rowell, Newton W., 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Rutgers College, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Sandwich, George Charles Montagu, 9th earl of, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Sandwich, Alberta (Sturges) Montagu, countess of, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Scott, James Brown, 1921-1922 (Box 19, Folder 100)
      See: box 15, folder 23; box 16, folder 35
      DELETE
    - Severance, Cordenio Arnold (Box 19, Folder 100)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 16, folder 38; box 17, folders 63-65
    - Shaw of Dunfermline, Thomas Shaw, baron, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Shelton, Thomas Wall, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Sherley, Swagar, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Shields, Randolph T., 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Shoecraft, Eugene, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - [Simon, Sir John Allsebrook], 1921 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Standard Oil Company (Box 19, Folder 102)
      See: box 15, folder 30
    - Stettinius, Edward R. (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 19, Folder 102)
      See: box 19, folder 111
    - Storey, Moorfield, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Strawn, Silas Hardy, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 102)
      See: box 14, folder 3; box 16, folder 37; box 17, folders 53-60
    - Strong, Charles Howard (Box 19, Folder 102)
      See: box 15, folder 24; box 16, folder 38
    - Stuart, Sir Campbell, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Sutherland, George, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Sweetser, Arthur (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Taylor, C. Burgess, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - Templeman, E. Bryan, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - Thompson, Huston, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Todd, G. Carroll, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Train, Arthur C., 1922 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Tucker, Henry St. George, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Tumulty, Joseph Patrick, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Underwood, E. Marvin, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Underwood, Oscar W., 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Vance, William Reynolds, 1921-1923 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Van Devanter, Willis, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Van Dyke, Henry (Box 19, Folder 106)
      See: box 18, folder 92
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Wallace, Hugh Campbell, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Warburg, Felix M. (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Warburg, Paul Moritz, 1921-1922 (Box 19, Folder 107)